{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934054446","data":{"timestamp":" 946934054446"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934064549","data":{"timestamp":" 946934064549"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934065082","data":{"timestamp":" 946934065082"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934065304","data":{"timestamp":" 946934065304"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934065987","data":{"timestamp":" 946934065986"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934067049","data":{"timestamp":" 946934067049"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934067982","data":{"timestamp":" 946934067982"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934068786","data":{"timestamp":" 946934068785"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934069609","data":{"timestamp":" 946934069609"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934073382","data":{"timestamp":" 946934073382"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934074205","data":{"timestamp":" 946934074205"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934074798","data":{"timestamp":" 946934074798"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934077309","data":{"timestamp":" 946934077309"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934078572","data":{"timestamp":" 946934078572"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" WALIWASAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934079355","data":{"timestamp":" 946934079355"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934080249","data":{"timestamp":" 946934080249"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934080723","data":{"timestamp":" 946934080722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934081596","data":{"timestamp":" 946934081596"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934084911","data":{"timestamp":" 946934084911"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934086425","data":{"timestamp":" 946934086424"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATAZWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATAZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934086877","data":{"timestamp":" 946934086877"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934087540","data":{"timestamp":" 946934087540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934087743","data":{"timestamp":" 946934087743"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934088336","data":{"timestamp":" 946934088336"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934091732","data":{"timestamp":" 946934091732"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934092195","data":{"timestamp":" 946934092195"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934092678","data":{"timestamp":" 946934092678"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934093672","data":{"timestamp":" 946934093672"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934094586","data":{"timestamp":" 946934094585"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934097441","data":{"timestamp":" 946934097441"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934097698","data":{"timestamp":" 946934097698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934097877","data":{"timestamp":" 946934097876"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934098541","data":{"timestamp":" 946934098541"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934099616","data":{"timestamp":" 946934099616"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934100500","data":{"timestamp":" 946934100500"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEUMBWA"," userResponse":" WAMEUMBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934100835","data":{"timestamp":" 946934100834"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934101378","data":{"timestamp":" 946934101378"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934104631","data":{"timestamp":" 946934104631"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934105297","data":{"timestamp":" 946934105297"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934105992","data":{"timestamp":" 946934105992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934107049","data":{"timestamp":" 946934107049"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934107500","data":{"timestamp":" 946934107499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934108196","data":{"timestamp":" 946934108195"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934109172","data":{"timestamp":" 946934109172"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934109416","data":{"timestamp":" 946934109415"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934110102","data":{"timestamp":" 946934110102"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANA"," userResponse":" MCHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934113192","data":{"timestamp":" 946934113191"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934113744","data":{"timestamp":" 946934113744"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934114699","data":{"timestamp":" 946934114699"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934114912","data":{"timestamp":" 946934114911"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934115356","data":{"timestamp":" 946934115355"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934115790","data":{"timestamp":" 946934115790"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934117135","data":{"timestamp":" 946934117135"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAZIDI"," userResponse":" IKAZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934119788","data":{"timestamp":" 946934119788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934120843","data":{"timestamp":" 946934120842"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONYA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934121596","data":{"timestamp":" 946934121596"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIENDE"," userResponse":" ASIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934122391","data":{"timestamp":" 946934122391"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934125359","data":{"timestamp":" 946934125359"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934126739","data":{"timestamp":" 946934126739"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUSIKIA"," userResponse":" HAKUSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934130203","data":{"timestamp":" 946934130203"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934130446","data":{"timestamp":" 946934130446"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934131032","data":{"timestamp":" 946934131032"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934131466","data":{"timestamp":" 946934131466"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934132169","data":{"timestamp":" 946934132169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934132983","data":{"timestamp":" 946934132983"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934136172","data":{"timestamp":" 946934136172"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934136407","data":{"timestamp":" 946934136407"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934136751","data":{"timestamp":" 946934136751"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934138297","data":{"timestamp":" 946934138297"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934139515","data":{"timestamp":" 946934139515"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOONA"," userResponse":" WALIPOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934139959","data":{"timestamp":" 946934139958"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934140442","data":{"timestamp":" 946934140442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934141707","data":{"timestamp":" 946934141706"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" AKIYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934145220","data":{"timestamp":" 946934145219"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAPANGA"," userResponse":" WAKAPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934145632","data":{"timestamp":" 946934145631"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934146367","data":{"timestamp":" 946934146366"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" FULANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934149222","data":{"timestamp":" 946934149222"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHUKUA"," userResponse":" WALICHUKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934149814","data":{"timestamp":" 946934149814"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934151132","data":{"timestamp":" 946934151131"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," userResponse":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934152611","data":{"timestamp":" 946934152610"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATENGEZA"," userResponse":" WAKATENGEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934153166","data":{"timestamp":" 946934153166"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934156535","data":{"timestamp":" 946934156534"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWEKA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934157076","data":{"timestamp":" 946934157076"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934157540","data":{"timestamp":" 946934157540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934157994","data":{"timestamp":" 946934157993"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934158254","data":{"timestamp":" 946934158253"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934158879","data":{"timestamp":" 946934158879"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934159623","data":{"timestamp":" 946934159623"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934162645","data":{"timestamp":" 946934162645"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934164030","data":{"timestamp":" 946934164029"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934165274","data":{"timestamp":" 946934165273"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934167360","data":{"timestamp":" 946934167359"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPEPERUKA"," userResponse":" AKAPEPERUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934168554","data":{"timestamp":" 946934168554"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934168910","data":{"timestamp":" 946934168910"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934169787","data":{"timestamp":" 946934169787"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934172383","data":{"timestamp":" 946934172382"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934172494","data":{"timestamp":" 946934172494"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a61def31-cce8-4bca-9d04-86a76e4e956c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934181288","data":{"timestamp":" 946934181287"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4c9b38b7-22f2-453d-b53d-d13919591560"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934183393","data":{"timestamp":" 946934183393"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4c9b38b7-22f2-453d-b53d-d13919591560"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934184371","data":{"timestamp":" 946934184371"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4c9b38b7-22f2-453d-b53d-d13919591560"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934184442","data":{"timestamp":" 946934184442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4c9b38b7-22f2-453d-b53d-d13919591560"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934217358","data":{"timestamp":" 946934217358"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934228606","data":{"timestamp":" 946934228606"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934239551","data":{"timestamp":" 946934239551"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934251322","data":{"timestamp":" 946934251322"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934262338","data":{"timestamp":" 946934262338"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934270902","data":{"timestamp":" 946934270902"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934281259","data":{"timestamp":" 946934281259"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934291391","data":{"timestamp":" 946934291391"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934302104","data":{"timestamp":" 946934302104"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934309705","data":{"timestamp":" 946934309705"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934312440","data":{"timestamp":" 946934312440"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934320994","data":{"timestamp":" 946934320994"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 72c2015f-9e34-46a3-845e-ffa985d55972"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934328681","data":{"timestamp":" 946934328681"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 0ae55db1-455f-498b-b669-fa88d3ad22a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_U-R-CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934330328","data":{"timestamp":" 946934330328"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 0ae55db1-455f-498b-b669-fa88d3ad22a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_U-R-CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934341481","data":{"timestamp":" 946934341481"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934342023","data":{"timestamp":" 946934342023"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934343516","data":{"timestamp":" 946934343515"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934344418","data":{"timestamp":" 946934344418"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934345141","data":{"timestamp":" 946934345141"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934345614","data":{"timestamp":" 946934345614"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934346407","data":{"timestamp":" 946934346407"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934349447","data":{"timestamp":" 946934349447"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934349660","data":{"timestamp":" 946934349659"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934350132","data":{"timestamp":" 946934350132"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934351035","data":{"timestamp":" 946934351034"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934352787","data":{"timestamp":" 946934352787"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TULIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934353559","data":{"timestamp":" 946934353558"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934354101","data":{"timestamp":" 946934354100"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934355525","data":{"timestamp":" 946934355524"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" ANGETUGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934356369","data":{"timestamp":" 946934356369"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934356939","data":{"timestamp":" 946934356938"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934360425","data":{"timestamp":" 946934360424"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934361774","data":{"timestamp":" 946934361773"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934363078","data":{"timestamp":" 946934363077"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934364738","data":{"timestamp":" 946934364738"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934367613","data":{"timestamp":" 946934367612"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" ALIYALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934368440","data":{"timestamp":" 946934368439"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934368721","data":{"timestamp":" 946934368721"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934369675","data":{"timestamp":" 946934369674"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934370785","data":{"timestamp":" 946934370784"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934371047","data":{"timestamp":" 946934371046"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934374065","data":{"timestamp":" 946934374064"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934374321","data":{"timestamp":" 946934374320"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934374815","data":{"timestamp":" 946934374814"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934375537","data":{"timestamp":" 946934375537"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934376953","data":{"timestamp":" 946934376952"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934378950","data":{"timestamp":" 946934378949"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULILIA"," userResponse":" TULILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934380444","data":{"timestamp":" 946934380443"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISEMA"," userResponse":" TUKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934381931","data":{"timestamp":" 946934381931"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934382114","data":{"timestamp":" 946934382114"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934383250","data":{"timestamp":" 946934383250"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934384275","data":{"timestamp":" 946934384274"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934384508","data":{"timestamp":" 946934384508"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934385511","data":{"timestamp":" 946934385511"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934388472","data":{"timestamp":" 946934388471"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934390205","data":{"timestamp":" 946934390205"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934391538","data":{"timestamp":" 946934391538"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934393014","data":{"timestamp":" 946934393013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934393732","data":{"timestamp":" 946934393731"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934395257","data":{"timestamp":" 946934395257"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934396120","data":{"timestamp":" 946934396120"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934397749","data":{"timestamp":" 946934397748"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934399115","data":{"timestamp":" 946934399114"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" YAMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934402014","data":{"timestamp":" 946934402013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934402243","data":{"timestamp":" 946934402243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934402713","data":{"timestamp":" 946934402712"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934403463","data":{"timestamp":" 946934403462"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934405207","data":{"timestamp":" 946934405206"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TULIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934405959","data":{"timestamp":" 946934405959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934406611","data":{"timestamp":" 946934406610"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934407372","data":{"timestamp":" 946934407371"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934408226","data":{"timestamp":" 946934408225"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934411768","data":{"timestamp":" 946934411767"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934412477","data":{"timestamp":" 946934412477"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934413656","data":{"timestamp":" 946934413655"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934415114","data":{"timestamp":" 946934415113"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934415758","data":{"timestamp":" 946934415758"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934419195","data":{"timestamp":" 946934419194"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934420046","data":{"timestamp":" 946934420046"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934421213","data":{"timestamp":" 946934421212"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934422669","data":{"timestamp":" 946934422669"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934423495","data":{"timestamp":" 946934423495"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934425429","data":{"timestamp":" 946934425428"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934428664","data":{"timestamp":" 946934428663"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934429977","data":{"timestamp":" 946934429977"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934431078","data":{"timestamp":" 946934431077"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934432356","data":{"timestamp":" 946934432354"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934433112","data":{"timestamp":" 946934433111"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934436156","data":{"timestamp":" 946934436155"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934437721","data":{"timestamp":" 946934437721"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934438634","data":{"timestamp":" 946934438633"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934438898","data":{"timestamp":" 946934438897"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934439743","data":{"timestamp":" 946934439742"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934439886","data":{"timestamp":" 946934439885"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934440583","data":{"timestamp":" 946934440582"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934442104","data":{"timestamp":" 946934442104"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" NAUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934442425","data":{"timestamp":" 946934442425"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934443147","data":{"timestamp":" 946934443147"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934446870","data":{"timestamp":" 946934446869"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934447788","data":{"timestamp":" 946934447787"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934448470","data":{"timestamp":" 946934448470"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934449496","data":{"timestamp":" 946934449496"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934450297","data":{"timestamp":" 946934450296"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934451060","data":{"timestamp":" 946934451060"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934451989","data":{"timestamp":" 946934451988"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934453104","data":{"timestamp":" 946934453102"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934453572","data":{"timestamp":" 946934453571"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934454424","data":{"timestamp":" 946934454423"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934455789","data":{"timestamp":" 946934455789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" ANGECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934455993","data":{"timestamp":" 946934455992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934456500","data":{"timestamp":" 946934456499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934460034","data":{"timestamp":" 946934460033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934461402","data":{"timestamp":" 946934461401"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPOPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934462064","data":{"timestamp":" 946934462064"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" NAFUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934463638","data":{"timestamp":" 946934463638"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934464938","data":{"timestamp":" 946934464937"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" ALITUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934466161","data":{"timestamp":" 946934466161"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934468768","data":{"timestamp":" 946934468767"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934468886","data":{"timestamp":" 946934468886"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934478293","data":{"timestamp":" 946934478293"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 8d3c9bce-d172-487f-ab1d-82befc2b5a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934508782","data":{"timestamp":" 946934508782"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934518109","data":{"timestamp":" 946934518109"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934527744","data":{"timestamp":" 946934527744"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934536529","data":{"timestamp":" 946934536529"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934546546","data":{"timestamp":" 946934546546"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934555263","data":{"timestamp":" 946934555263"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934565533","data":{"timestamp":" 946934565533"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934575489","data":{"timestamp":" 946934575489"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934582644","data":{"timestamp":" 946934582644"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934592666","data":{"timestamp":" 946934592666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934600834","data":{"timestamp":" 946934600834"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934603566","data":{"timestamp":" 946934603566"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934612313","data":{"timestamp":" 946934612312"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd0578c-0be3-4910-b260-f807ae15eb36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934633125","data":{"timestamp":" 946934633125"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_B_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934639804","data":{"timestamp":" 946934639804"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_Y_CH"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934646452","data":{"timestamp":" 946934646451"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_CH_S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934653125","data":{"timestamp":" 946934653125"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_CH_V_Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934659775","data":{"timestamp":" 946934659775"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_CH_F_Z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934666423","data":{"timestamp":" 946934666423"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_J_CH"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934673076","data":{"timestamp":" 946934673076"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_CH_V"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934679729","data":{"timestamp":" 946934679729"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_CH_Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934686342","data":{"timestamp":" 946934686342"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_CH_U_F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934692998","data":{"timestamp":" 946934692997"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_W_CH"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934706182","data":{"timestamp":" 946934706181"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 55505481-7d9f-4141-b1ab-b75f12295bf1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_D_W_CH"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934719028","data":{"timestamp":" 946934719028"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934719600","data":{"timestamp":" 946934719600"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934719820","data":{"timestamp":" 946934719820"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934720321","data":{"timestamp":" 946934720321"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934721598","data":{"timestamp":" 946934721598"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934721840","data":{"timestamp":" 946934721839"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934722423","data":{"timestamp":" 946934722422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934722756","data":{"timestamp":" 946934722755"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934723429","data":{"timestamp":" 946934723429"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na Jimbi na Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934726243","data":{"timestamp":" 946934726242"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934727174","data":{"timestamp":" 946934727173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934728070","data":{"timestamp":" 946934728068"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa marafiki wakubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUBWA"," userResponse":" WAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934731136","data":{"timestamp":" 946934731136"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934731901","data":{"timestamp":" 946934731900"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934733034","data":{"timestamp":" 946934733033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934734350","data":{"timestamp":" 946934734350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTEMBELEA"," userResponse":" ALIMTEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934734910","data":{"timestamp":" 946934734909"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934735571","data":{"timestamp":" 946934735571"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934736514","data":{"timestamp":" 946934736514"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934736836","data":{"timestamp":" 946934736835"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934740105","data":{"timestamp":" 946934740105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" WALIFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934740880","data":{"timestamp":" 946934740879"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934741129","data":{"timestamp":" 946934741129"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934741796","data":{"timestamp":" 946934741795"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934742592","data":{"timestamp":" 946934742592"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifurahia chakula cha jioni pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934745667","data":{"timestamp":" 946934745667"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934745858","data":{"timestamp":" 946934745858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934746319","data":{"timestamp":" 946934746318"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934747096","data":{"timestamp":" 946934747096"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934748322","data":{"timestamp":" 946934748322"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa kwenda kulala ulifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFIKA"," userResponse":" ULIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934751096","data":{"timestamp":" 946934751096"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934752052","data":{"timestamp":" 946934752052"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934752692","data":{"timestamp":" 946934752692"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934753686","data":{"timestamp":" 946934753685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934754416","data":{"timestamp":" 946934754416"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934755323","data":{"timestamp":" 946934755323"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934755571","data":{"timestamp":" 946934755571"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934756671","data":{"timestamp":" 946934756670"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOLALA"," userResponse":" WALIPOLALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934757777","data":{"timestamp":" 946934757776"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934758444","data":{"timestamp":" 946934758443"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAO"," userResponse":" VYAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934759932","data":{"timestamp":" 946934759931"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walipolala vichwa vyao vilifichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIFICHWA"," userResponse":" VILIFICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934763044","data":{"timestamp":" 946934763044"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934763907","data":{"timestamp":" 946934763906"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934764475","data":{"timestamp":" 946934764475"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934765165","data":{"timestamp":" 946934765165"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934765734","data":{"timestamp":" 946934765733"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934766394","data":{"timestamp":" 946934766393"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934767002","data":{"timestamp":" 946934767002"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934768270","data":{"timestamp":" 946934768269"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILALA"," userResponse":" WALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934769657","data":{"timestamp":" 946934769657"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura aliona kwamba Jimbi na familia yake walilala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" FOFOFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934772105","data":{"timestamp":" 946934772105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934773124","data":{"timestamp":" 946934773123"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934773937","data":{"timestamp":" 946934773937"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934774722","data":{"timestamp":" 946934774722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934775282","data":{"timestamp":" 946934775281"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yeye hakuweza kulala usiku kucha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHA"," userResponse":" KUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934778779","data":{"timestamp":" 946934778776"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934779431","data":{"timestamp":" 946934779430"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934780303","data":{"timestamp":" 946934780303"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAKA"," userResponse":" ALITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934780990","data":{"timestamp":" 946934780988"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJUA"," userResponse":" KUJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934781664","data":{"timestamp":" 946934781664"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934781759","data":{"timestamp":" 946934781759"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934782340","data":{"timestamp":" 946934782340"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934784831","data":{"timestamp":" 946934784830"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINYI"," userResponse":" NINYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934785548","data":{"timestamp":" 946934785547"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWEKA"," userResponse":" HUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934786059","data":{"timestamp":" 946934786059"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934786518","data":{"timestamp":" 946934786517"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934787095","data":{"timestamp":" 946934787095"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYENU"," userResponse":" VYENU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934788100","data":{"timestamp":" 946934788100"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninyi huweka wapi vichwa vyenu usiku?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934790996","data":{"timestamp":" 946934790995"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934792586","data":{"timestamp":" 946934792585"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934793679","data":{"timestamp":" 946934793678"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KUMCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934794296","data":{"timestamp":" 946934794296"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHERE"," userResponse":" SHERE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934795198","data":{"timestamp":" 946934795198"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jimbi aliamua kumchezea shere Sungura."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934797856","data":{"timestamp":" 946934797855"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934798904","data":{"timestamp":" 946934798904"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934799380","data":{"timestamp":" 946934799380"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934800421","data":{"timestamp":" 946934800421"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934801106","data":{"timestamp":" 946934801105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934802104","data":{"timestamp":" 946934802104"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNA"," userResponse":" TUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934802700","data":{"timestamp":" 946934802700"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934802787","data":{"timestamp":" 946934802787"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934803512","data":{"timestamp":" 946934803512"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934805934","data":{"timestamp":" 946934805933"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934806122","data":{"timestamp":" 946934806122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934806900","data":{"timestamp":" 946934806899"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934807971","data":{"timestamp":" 946934807971"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934808781","data":{"timestamp":" 946934808780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKATA"," userResponse":" HUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934809222","data":{"timestamp":" 946934809222"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934809632","data":{"timestamp":" 946934809632"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYETU"," userResponse":" VYETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934811852","data":{"timestamp":" 946934811852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934812523","data":{"timestamp":" 946934812523"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934813410","data":{"timestamp":" 946934813410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934814104","data":{"timestamp":" 946934814104"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULALA"," userResponse":" HULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934815140","data":{"timestamp":" 946934815140"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEMA"," userResponse":" VYEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934815907","data":{"timestamp":" 946934815906"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila vichwa sisi hulala vyema kabisa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934818808","data":{"timestamp":" 946934818806"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934819952","data":{"timestamp":" 946934819952"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934820757","data":{"timestamp":" 946934820757"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934821920","data":{"timestamp":" 946934821920"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUVIREJESHA"," userResponse":" HUVIREJESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934822475","data":{"timestamp":" 946934822475"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934823056","data":{"timestamp":" 946934823056"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYETU"," userResponse":" VYETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934823835","data":{"timestamp":" 946934823835"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934824710","data":{"timestamp":" 946934824709"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934825878","data":{"timestamp":" 946934825877"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha asubuhi sisi huvirejesha vichwa vyetu mwilini Jimbi alieleza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIELEZA"," userResponse":" ALIELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934829294","data":{"timestamp":" 946934829294"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934830310","data":{"timestamp":" 946934830310"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934831297","data":{"timestamp":" 946934831296"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934831858","data":{"timestamp":" 946934831858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934833142","data":{"timestamp":" 946934833142"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUIAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934834125","data":{"timestamp":" 946934834125"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934834469","data":{"timestamp":" 946934834468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934835431","data":{"timestamp":" 946934835430"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934835580","data":{"timestamp":" 946934835580"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934836215","data":{"timestamp":" 946934836214"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sungura alikwenda nyumbani na kuiambia familia yake siri ya kuku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934838922","data":{"timestamp":" 946934838922"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934839188","data":{"timestamp":" 946934839188"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934839966","data":{"timestamp":" 946934839965"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934840999","data":{"timestamp":" 946934840998"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMUA"," userResponse":" ILIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934842513","data":{"timestamp":" 946934842512"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJARIBU"," userResponse":" KUJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934842844","data":{"timestamp":" 946934842844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934843648","data":{"timestamp":" 946934843648"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia ya Sungura iliamua kujaribu wao wenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934846534","data":{"timestamp":" 946934846534"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" UNAFIKIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934846990","data":{"timestamp":" 946934846990"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934848557","data":{"timestamp":" 946934848557"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934851311","data":{"timestamp":" 946934851309"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934851394","data":{"timestamp":" 946934851394"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934861650","data":{"timestamp":" 946934861650"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 3fd00e0b-e517-40fc-aedf-e1e1ec873234"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934871402","data":{"timestamp":" 946934871402"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934872492","data":{"timestamp":" 946934872491"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHESABU"," userResponse":" KUHESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934873424","data":{"timestamp":" 946934873423"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBA"," userResponse":" NAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934876709","data":{"timestamp":" 946934876709"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934877210","data":{"timestamp":" 946934877210"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934877841","data":{"timestamp":" 946934877841"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934880981","data":{"timestamp":" 946934880979"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934881796","data":{"timestamp":" 946934881795"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934882203","data":{"timestamp":" 946934882202"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934882946","data":{"timestamp":" 946934882946"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934886101","data":{"timestamp":" 946934886101"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934886732","data":{"timestamp":" 946934886731"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934887275","data":{"timestamp":" 946934887274"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934890381","data":{"timestamp":" 946934890380"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934890460","data":{"timestamp":" 946934890460"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 80788e4d-4897-462a-a78c-7c052f6f3256"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934902159","data":{"timestamp":" 946934902159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934903241","data":{"timestamp":" 946934903240"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHESABU"," userResponse":" KUHESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934904169","data":{"timestamp":" 946934904168"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua kuhesabu namba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMBA"," userResponse":" NAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934907481","data":{"timestamp":" 946934907480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934907985","data":{"timestamp":" 946934907985"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934908616","data":{"timestamp":" 946934908615"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934911646","data":{"timestamp":" 946934911646"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934912439","data":{"timestamp":" 946934912438"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934912831","data":{"timestamp":" 946934912831"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934913565","data":{"timestamp":" 946934913565"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934916659","data":{"timestamp":" 946934916659"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934917283","data":{"timestamp":" 946934917282"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934917816","data":{"timestamp":" 946934917816"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Number_Song_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934920808","data":{"timestamp":" 946934920807"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934920875","data":{"timestamp":" 946934920875"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934928639","data":{"timestamp":" 946934928639"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 4d018111-d61d-4235-b24d-8277d65da0d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Number_Song_2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nane tisa kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934939099","data":{"timestamp":" 946934939098"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934939693","data":{"timestamp":" 946934939692"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934940414","data":{"timestamp":" 946934940414"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934940592","data":{"timestamp":" 946934940592"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934941380","data":{"timestamp":" 946934941380"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934942416","data":{"timestamp":" 946934942414"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934945216","data":{"timestamp":" 946934945216"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TULIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934945907","data":{"timestamp":" 946934945907"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" FOLENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934947173","data":{"timestamp":" 946934947173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934948844","data":{"timestamp":" 946934948844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934949602","data":{"timestamp":" 946934949602"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" KUCHOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934950450","data":{"timestamp":" 946934950450"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934951330","data":{"timestamp":" 946934951330"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934952068","data":{"timestamp":" 946934952068"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934952751","data":{"timestamp":" 946934952751"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934956393","data":{"timestamp":" 946934956393"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TULISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934956932","data":{"timestamp":" 946934956932"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934957089","data":{"timestamp":" 946934957088"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934957493","data":{"timestamp":" 946934957493"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934958327","data":{"timestamp":" 946934958326"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934959268","data":{"timestamp":" 946934959268"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" KUPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934959973","data":{"timestamp":" 946934959973"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934960126","data":{"timestamp":" 946934960126"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934960895","data":{"timestamp":" 946934960895"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934963972","data":{"timestamp":" 946934963972"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TULIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934964445","data":{"timestamp":" 946934964445"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934964958","data":{"timestamp":" 946934964958"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934965731","data":{"timestamp":" 946934965731"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934966375","data":{"timestamp":" 946934966375"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934967008","data":{"timestamp":" 946934967008"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934967092","data":{"timestamp":" 946934967092"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934967685","data":{"timestamp":" 946934967685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" WIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934970882","data":{"timestamp":" 946934970882"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934971016","data":{"timestamp":" 946934971016"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934971949","data":{"timestamp":" 946934971949"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934973027","data":{"timestamp":" 946934973027"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934973686","data":{"timestamp":" 946934973686"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934974139","data":{"timestamp":" 946934974137"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934974762","data":{"timestamp":" 946934974762"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934975301","data":{"timestamp":" 946934975300"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934975790","data":{"timestamp":" 946934975789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934977154","data":{"timestamp":" 946934977154"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934977798","data":{"timestamp":" 946934977798"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" KULIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934978381","data":{"timestamp":" 946934978381"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934981383","data":{"timestamp":" 946934981383"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934981758","data":{"timestamp":" 946934981757"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934982740","data":{"timestamp":" 946934982740"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934983244","data":{"timestamp":" 946934983244"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934984197","data":{"timestamp":" 946934984197"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934984840","data":{"timestamp":" 946934984840"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934985453","data":{"timestamp":" 946934985453"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" YAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934988442","data":{"timestamp":" 946934988442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934989186","data":{"timestamp":" 946934989186"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934990000","data":{"timestamp":" 946934990000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" WALIRANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934990493","data":{"timestamp":" 946934990493"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" RANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934991427","data":{"timestamp":" 946934991427"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934992062","data":{"timestamp":" 946934992061"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934992666","data":{"timestamp":" 946934992666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934993601","data":{"timestamp":" 946934993600"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934994045","data":{"timestamp":" 946934994044"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934994507","data":{"timestamp":" 946934994507"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934995471","data":{"timestamp":" 946934995470"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MASHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934998577","data":{"timestamp":" 946934998577"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946934999870","data":{"timestamp":" 946934999870"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIPOVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935001604","data":{"timestamp":" 946935001604"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935002398","data":{"timestamp":" 946935002398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935003232","data":{"timestamp":" 946935003232"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" CHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935003696","data":{"timestamp":" 946935003696"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935004909","data":{"timestamp":" 946935004909"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" KUZIANGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935005932","data":{"timestamp":" 946935005932"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935006386","data":{"timestamp":" 946935006386"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935006999","data":{"timestamp":" 946935006999"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" UANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935010431","data":{"timestamp":" 946935010431"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935011024","data":{"timestamp":" 946935011024"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935011947","data":{"timestamp":" 946935011947"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935012131","data":{"timestamp":" 946935012131"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935012865","data":{"timestamp":" 946935012864"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935013107","data":{"timestamp":" 946935013107"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935013730","data":{"timestamp":" 946935013730"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935015113","data":{"timestamp":" 946935015113"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935015457","data":{"timestamp":" 946935015457"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935015930","data":{"timestamp":" 946935015930"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935019510","data":{"timestamp":" 946935019509"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935019952","data":{"timestamp":" 946935019952"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935020595","data":{"timestamp":" 946935020595"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935021879","data":{"timestamp":" 946935021878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935022073","data":{"timestamp":" 946935022072"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935022667","data":{"timestamp":" 946935022666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935023894","data":{"timestamp":" 946935023892"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935024578","data":{"timestamp":" 946935024578"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935025422","data":{"timestamp":" 946935025422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" MITUNGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935025846","data":{"timestamp":" 946935025846"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935026980","data":{"timestamp":" 946935026980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935027694","data":{"timestamp":" 946935027693"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935030855","data":{"timestamp":" 946935030855"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935032100","data":{"timestamp":" 946935032099"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935032864","data":{"timestamp":" 946935032864"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935033488","data":{"timestamp":" 946935033488"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935034262","data":{"timestamp":" 946935034261"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935034816","data":{"timestamp":" 946935034815"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935036119","data":{"timestamp":" 946935036119"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" AKIWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935036633","data":{"timestamp":" 946935036632"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935037867","data":{"timestamp":" 946935037867"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935038692","data":{"timestamp":" 946935038692"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935038906","data":{"timestamp":" 946935038905"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935039719","data":{"timestamp":" 946935039719"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" KUJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935042530","data":{"timestamp":" 946935042530"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935043773","data":{"timestamp":" 946935043773"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935044337","data":{"timestamp":" 946935044337"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935044420","data":{"timestamp":" 946935044420"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935044844","data":{"timestamp":" 946935044844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935045397","data":{"timestamp":" 946935045397"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935045791","data":{"timestamp":" 946935045791"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935046714","data":{"timestamp":" 946935046714"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935047569","data":{"timestamp":" 946935047569"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TULIPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935048133","data":{"timestamp":" 946935048133"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935048376","data":{"timestamp":" 946935048376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935049130","data":{"timestamp":" 946935049129"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935052165","data":{"timestamp":" 946935052165"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935053049","data":{"timestamp":" 946935053048"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935054162","data":{"timestamp":" 946935054162"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935054637","data":{"timestamp":" 946935054636"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935055501","data":{"timestamp":" 946935055501"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935055895","data":{"timestamp":" 946935055895"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935056629","data":{"timestamp":" 946935056629"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935057933","data":{"timestamp":" 946935057933"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935059136","data":{"timestamp":" 946935059136"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TUREKEBISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935059680","data":{"timestamp":" 946935059680"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935060315","data":{"timestamp":" 946935060314"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935063799","data":{"timestamp":" 946935063799"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935065003","data":{"timestamp":" 946935065003"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935065857","data":{"timestamp":" 946935065857"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" AMEPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935066461","data":{"timestamp":" 946935066461"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935067374","data":{"timestamp":" 946935067374"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935067658","data":{"timestamp":" 946935067658"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935068312","data":{"timestamp":" 946935068312"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935069336","data":{"timestamp":" 946935069335"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935070419","data":{"timestamp":" 946935070419"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" KUSAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935071053","data":{"timestamp":" 946935071052"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935071206","data":{"timestamp":" 946935071206"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935071610","data":{"timestamp":" 946935071610"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935072314","data":{"timestamp":" 946935072314"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935075470","data":{"timestamp":" 946935075469"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935076023","data":{"timestamp":" 946935076023"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935076196","data":{"timestamp":" 946935076196"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935076960","data":{"timestamp":" 946935076960"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" MAKAMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935077763","data":{"timestamp":" 946935077763"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935078740","data":{"timestamp":" 946935078740"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935079694","data":{"timestamp":" 946935079694"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935080678","data":{"timestamp":" 946935080677"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935081422","data":{"timestamp":" 946935081422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" KUUNGANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935081605","data":{"timestamp":" 946935081605"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935082199","data":{"timestamp":" 946935082199"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935082983","data":{"timestamp":" 946935082983"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935086072","data":{"timestamp":" 946935086071"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935086905","data":{"timestamp":" 946935086905"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935087859","data":{"timestamp":" 946935087859"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935088053","data":{"timestamp":" 946935088052"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935088697","data":{"timestamp":" 946935088696"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935089870","data":{"timestamp":" 946935089870"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935090764","data":{"timestamp":" 946935090764"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" WATACHIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935091327","data":{"timestamp":" 946935091327"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935091581","data":{"timestamp":" 946935091580"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935092264","data":{"timestamp":" 946935092263"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935095420","data":{"timestamp":" 946935095420"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935096294","data":{"timestamp":" 946935096294"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TULISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935096527","data":{"timestamp":" 946935096527"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935097181","data":{"timestamp":" 946935097181"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935097664","data":{"timestamp":" 946935097664"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935099028","data":{"timestamp":" 946935099028"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935100164","data":{"timestamp":" 946935100164"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TUBADILISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935100894","data":{"timestamp":" 946935100894"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935101604","data":{"timestamp":" 946935101604"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935104002","data":{"timestamp":" 946935104001"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935104479","data":{"timestamp":" 946935104478"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935105125","data":{"timestamp":" 946935105124"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935106199","data":{"timestamp":" 946935106199"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935106692","data":{"timestamp":" 946935106691"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935107680","data":{"timestamp":" 946935107680"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935109097","data":{"timestamp":" 946935109096"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATATUA"," userResponse":" TUKATATUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935109597","data":{"timestamp":" 946935109597"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935109962","data":{"timestamp":" 946935109962"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935112832","data":{"timestamp":" 946935112831"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935112950","data":{"timestamp":" 946935112949"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935121106","data":{"timestamp":" 946935121105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 00de8b3d-bef1-40e5-893f-69036212320a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935132094","data":{"timestamp":" 946935132093"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-7-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935138060","data":{"timestamp":" 946935138060"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-3-8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935144373","data":{"timestamp":" 946935144372"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-5-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935150453","data":{"timestamp":" 946935150452"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-8-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935158020","data":{"timestamp":" 946935158019"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-5-9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935164196","data":{"timestamp":" 946935164196"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935170617","data":{"timestamp":" 946935170617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935176963","data":{"timestamp":" 946935176963"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_0-2-8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935183104","data":{"timestamp":" 946935183104"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_6-0-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935188330","data":{"timestamp":" 946935188330"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-6-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935195058","data":{"timestamp":" 946935195057"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-6-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935201484","data":{"timestamp":" 946935201484"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-6-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935213181","data":{"timestamp":" 946935213181"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2051db03-9990-4bd7-8f04-aa8cce3a4157"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.mc.25"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-6-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935213244","data":{"timestamp":" 946935213244"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" ae97ffc3-bf3a-4f92-9978-754582536d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935220033","data":{"timestamp":" 946935220033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" ae97ffc3-bf3a-4f92-9978-754582536d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935238878","data":{"timestamp":" 946935238878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935255229","data":{"timestamp":" 946935255228"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935263564","data":{"timestamp":" 946935263564"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935271894","data":{"timestamp":" 946935271894"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935282039","data":{"timestamp":" 946935282039"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935292526","data":{"timestamp":" 946935292526"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935301542","data":{"timestamp":" 946935301542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935310611","data":{"timestamp":" 946935310611"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935320422","data":{"timestamp":" 946935320422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935329918","data":{"timestamp":" 946935329918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935338540","data":{"timestamp":" 946935338540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935342206","data":{"timestamp":" 946935342206"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935345584","data":{"timestamp":" 946935345584"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935353071","data":{"timestamp":" 946935353071"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935363963","data":{"timestamp":" 946935363962"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935372993","data":{"timestamp":" 946935372992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935550796","data":{"timestamp":" 946935550795"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a031e7cf-060b-4e5f-a41d-4ad3a20a3b6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935550925","data":{"timestamp":" 946935550925"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" f486cf78-ada9-4de4-9bd9-10c06c4c5246"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935570902","data":{"timestamp":" 946935570902"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_T_M"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935577581","data":{"timestamp":" 946935577581"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_P_D"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935584266","data":{"timestamp":" 946935584265"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_T_R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935590976","data":{"timestamp":" 946935590975"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_G_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935597660","data":{"timestamp":" 946935597659"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_L_D"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935604360","data":{"timestamp":" 946935604359"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_K_T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935611021","data":{"timestamp":" 946935611021"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_D_R"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935618525","data":{"timestamp":" 946935618525"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_D_R"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935625210","data":{"timestamp":" 946935625209"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_N_W"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935631875","data":{"timestamp":" 946935631875"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_P_Y"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935638603","data":{"timestamp":" 946935638601"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_S_D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:D..D.all.10.rand.say.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935651697","data":{"timestamp":" 946935651696"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" a997506e-4fdd-49ab-be6e-2703895b7721"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_D..D.all.10.rand.say.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_N_S_D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935663189","data":{"timestamp":" 946935663188"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2f884f55-035a-47e2-90db-207e4275d78a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935668394","data":{"timestamp":" 946935668394"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2f884f55-035a-47e2-90db-207e4275d78a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935673550","data":{"timestamp":" 946935673550"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 2f884f55-035a-47e2-90db-207e4275d78a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936652772","data":{"timestamp":" 946936652772"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 6e4a248f-385f-432c-823d-0c3c9070d42e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-8-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936658590","data":{"timestamp":" 946936658590"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 6e4a248f-385f-432c-823d-0c3c9070d42e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-8-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936663552","data":{"timestamp":" 946936663552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 6e4a248f-385f-432c-823d-0c3c9070d42e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-8-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936672492","data":{"timestamp":" 946936672492"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 6e4a248f-385f-432c-823d-0c3c9070d42e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-3-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936680098","data":{"timestamp":" 946936680097"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 6e4a248f-385f-432c-823d-0c3c9070d42e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-3-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936691617","data":{"timestamp":" 946936691617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 6e4a248f-385f-432c-823d-0c3c9070d42e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936726460","data":{"timestamp":" 946936726460"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 6e4a248f-385f-432c-823d-0c3c9070d42e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-2-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936732459","data":{"timestamp":" 946936732457"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 6e4a248f-385f-432c-823d-0c3c9070d42e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-2-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936746366","data":{"timestamp":" 946936746366"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 970fba5c-a5fc-42ed-9da4-4ffe784fd540"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936747780","data":{"timestamp":" 946936747780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 970fba5c-a5fc-42ed-9da4-4ffe784fd540"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936906234","data":{"timestamp":" 946936906233"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 970fba5c-a5fc-42ed-9da4-4ffe784fd540"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936906347","data":{"timestamp":" 946936906347"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" c03d927d-5326-4b14-9ba6-b588f676654d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936915992","data":{"timestamp":" 946936915992"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" c03d927d-5326-4b14-9ba6-b588f676654d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936926230","data":{"timestamp":" 946936926230"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" c03d927d-5326-4b14-9ba6-b588f676654d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936976324","data":{"timestamp":" 946936976324"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" c03d927d-5326-4b14-9ba6-b588f676654d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936994722","data":{"timestamp":" 946936994722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 62b8b9cb-8ab7-4241-8f07-a684f22a2940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946936994878","data":{"timestamp":" 946936994878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 62b8b9cb-8ab7-4241-8f07-a684f22a2940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937002347","data":{"timestamp":" 946937002347"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 62b8b9cb-8ab7-4241-8f07-a684f22a2940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937012487","data":{"timestamp":" 946937012486"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 62b8b9cb-8ab7-4241-8f07-a684f22a2940"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937022538","data":{"timestamp":" 946937022538"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" c5acb9e8-5ab5-45a7-bdd8-a50993226d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_5-2-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937029418","data":{"timestamp":" 946937029418"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" c5acb9e8-5ab5-45a7-bdd8-a50993226d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-3-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937032194","data":{"timestamp":" 946937032193"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" c5acb9e8-5ab5-45a7-bdd8-a50993226d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-3-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937042365","data":{"timestamp":" 946937042365"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937044516","data":{"timestamp":" 946937044516"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937046618","data":{"timestamp":" 946937046618"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937049776","data":{"timestamp":" 946937049775"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937052000","data":{"timestamp":" 946937052000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937054220","data":{"timestamp":" 946937054220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937057032","data":{"timestamp":" 946937057032"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937059203","data":{"timestamp":" 946937059203"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937061369","data":{"timestamp":" 946937061369"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937064635","data":{"timestamp":" 946937064635"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937066685","data":{"timestamp":" 946937066685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937068749","data":{"timestamp":" 946937068748"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937076442","data":{"timestamp":" 946937076442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937078695","data":{"timestamp":" 946937078695"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937080892","data":{"timestamp":" 946937080892"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937083852","data":{"timestamp":" 946937083852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937086308","data":{"timestamp":" 946937086308"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_001400"," gameId":" 25aeeeee-93c9-4dc0-9bec-a78fecb05a1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}